Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Images from Murree, Pakistan (see also Ref4), a Visit to Concord Aircraft Factory, and Al Ain
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with an unidentified man on a train., April 1971; AD_MC_093_ref30_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.5 x 12.6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Trains; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Drinks/Beverages; Unknown Locations
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (front, left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front, right) on a personal trip to Murree, Pakistan., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref30_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Forest/Woodlands; Pakistan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) on a lawn in Murree, Pakistan., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref30_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Forest/Woodlands; Pakistan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) playing carrom in Murree, Pakistan., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref30_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Card Games; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Pakistan; Drinks/Beverages
  - A contact sheet from the UAE trip to the Concord Aircraft Factory in the United Kingdom., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref30_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10.9 x 20 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Factories; Women; Group Portraits; London, England, UK; Airplanes; Transportation; Sheikhs; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Bridges; Water; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan at an al falaj well in Al Ain., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref30_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Individual Portraits; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Presidents; Royalty; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Deserts; Camels; Animals
- Studio Portraits of UAE Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.4 x 4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; United Arab Emirates
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Sultan Bin Khalifa Bin Zayed., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref31_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5.5 x 4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Individual Portraits; Royalty; Sheikhs; United Arab Emirates; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of H.H. Sheikh Saeed Al Mubarak Al Qaitbay., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5.5 x 4.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of a man that worked for H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., 12 Jan 1968; AD_MC_093_ref31_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 4.4 x 7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Individual Portraits; Officials; English Writing; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Dr. Mohammed Saeed Al Badi in military uniform., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 6.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Dr. Mohammed Saeed Al Badi., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 6.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of Mohammed Saeed Al Farad in Dibba Al-Fujairah., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref31_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Men; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Facial Hair; Fujairah, United Arab Emirates; Buildings
- Album of Assorted Images of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr
  - The front cover of an album of assorted images of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1950-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.7 x 25.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    United Arab Emirates; Paris, France; Unknown Locations; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) with an unidentified man and three members of the Abu Dhabi military., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Cameras; United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with a group of men during a unification talk., Circa 1969-1971; AD_MC_093_ref32_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Gatherings; Politics; Government; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Microphones; Facial Hair
  - H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed (middle) and H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Bin Saeed (right of Sheikh Rashid) with a group of men on a tour., Circa 1955-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 16.3 x 21 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Unknown Locations; Sheikhs; Gatherings; Royalty; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - From the left: a group portrait of Sheikh Hasher bin Maktoum Al Maktoum, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and Sheikh Ahmad bin Maktoum Al Maktoum., Circa 1963-1964; AD_MC_093_ref32_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 10.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Group Portraits
  - An aerial view of Jamal Abdel Nasser Square in Dubai., Circa 1960-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9.1 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Street Lamps; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Mosques; Religious Sites; Shops; Signs/Signposts
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) reaching his hand towards another man in the desert., Circa 1958-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Mountains/Hills; United Arab Emirates; Officials; Deserts
  - Front row, from the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki with a group of men behind them, including H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed (behind Sheikh Zayed) at the Al Ain Palace Hotel., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.6 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Signs/Signposts; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Hotels; Flags; Gatherings; Men
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr driving a car with three people in the passenger seat in Dubai., Circa 1956-1960; AD_MC_093_ref32_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr leaning on a truck., Circa 1956-1960; AD_MC_093_ref32_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Officials; Men; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Unknown Locations
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in a wooded area., Circa 1956-1960; AD_MC_093_ref32_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Forest/Woodlands; Unknown Locations
  - A man holding a shotgun outside of an arish hut, Circa 1945-1955; AD_MC_093_ref32_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Guns; Weapons; Individual Portraits; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Hunting; Birds; Animals
  - A group of people inside a cafeteria in Dubai., Circa 1945-1955; AD_MC_093_ref32_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Restaurants/bars; Signs/Signposts; Streets/Roads; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children
  - Sheikh Hasher bin Maktoum Al Maktoum (left) sitting with an unidentified man., Circa 1960-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 10.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr during a trip to Paris with members of the Emirati delegation in the background., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Paris, France; Individual Portraits; Streets/Roads; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) sitting on sofas with two unidentified men., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10.5 x 15 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations; Officials; Furnishings
  - A view of the Eiffel Tower., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Eiffel Tower; Streets/Roads; Paris, France; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Street Lamps; Buildings; Architecture
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Mubarak bin Qarran Al Mansoori in a garden in Paris., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gardens; Officials; Sheikhs; Paris, France; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - A studio portrait of Sheikh Hasher bin Maktoum Al Maktoum., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12 x 8.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Sheikhs; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Studio Photography; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr performing the Al Ayala dance with a crowd of men behind him., Circa 1965-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Crowds; Dancing; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Gatherings; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with Ibrahim Al Hadidi Al Shamsi at the Diwan in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10.5 x 7.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Carpets/Rugs; Offices
  - H.H. Sheikh Ahmad bin Ali Al Thani and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (background) upon Sheikh Ahmed's arrival to Abu Dhabi., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.3 x 10.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr reading a book., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 10.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Books; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - ?, AD_MC_093_ref32_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr performing the Al Ayala dance with a crowd of men behind him., Circa 1965-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Crowds; Gatherings; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Dancing; Swords/Knives; Weapons; United Arab Emirates; Percussion Instruments; Musical Instruments
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) at a dinner for a delegation., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Food; Gatherings; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Drinks/Beverages; United Arab Emirates
  - A portrait of a man smoking a cigarette., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000027_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Smoking; Unknown Locations; Furnishings
  - ?, AD_MC_093_ref32_000028_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - From the left: H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki, an unidentified man, H.H. Sheikh Ahmad bin Ali Al Thani, H.E. Hamdan Bin Hamed Al Nahyan, Mohammed Bin Khalid Al Nahyan, Mubarak Bin Hamed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a tour., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000029_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.4 x 10.6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Crowds; Buildings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - An unidentified man (left) smoking with Mohammed Badr (right)., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000030_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Smoking; Unknown Locations; Cameras; Clocks/Watches
  - A group portrait of students from the United Arab Emirates in Cairo., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000031_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Cairo, Egypt; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Art; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) with an unidentified man (left) on a plane., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000032_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Airplanes; Transportation; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty
  - A view of abras in the Dubai Creek., Circa 1950-1955; AD_MC_093_ref32_000033_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Rivers; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - ?, AD_MC_093_ref32_000034_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - A portrait of H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi in H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's office., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000035_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 21.5 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Offices; United Arab Emirates
  - The back cover of an album of assorted images of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1950-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000036_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.7 x 25.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; United Arab Emirates; Paris, France; Unknown Locations; Cairo, Egypt
- Continental Circus in Dubai 24 May 1972
  - The front cover of the album "Continental Circus in Dubai 24 May 1972.", May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - The inside front cover of the album "Continental Circus in Dubai 24 May 1972.", May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; English Writing
  - From the top down: a view of the Continental Circus tent; a group of men at the Continental Circus, including H.H. Sheikh Hamed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (fourth from the left); and performers at the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Tents; Gatherings; Performing Arts; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Electricity; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Royalty; Women; Flags; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Events/Occasions
  - Three views of H.H. Sheikh Hamed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (middle, with walking stick) entering the Continental Circus with a group of men., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Royalty; Officials; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Gatherings; Canes/Walking Sticks; Boys; Children; Clocks/Watches; Events/Occasions
  - Top: H.H. Sheikh Hamed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum cutting a ribbon at the opening ceremony of the Continental Circus. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Hamed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum speaking to a group of people at the opening ceremony of the Continental Circus, May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Performing Arts; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Girls; Children; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Audiences/Spectators; Events/Occasions
  - Top: performers at the Continental Circus. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Hamed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (middle) with a group of men watching the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Performing Arts; Tents; Gatherings; Costumes; Sheikhs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Boys; Children; Audiences/Spectators; Clocks/Watches; Events/Occasions
  - Top: performers at the Continental Circus. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Hamed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (second from the right) with a group of men watching the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Women; Individual Portraits; Costumes; Tents; Performing Arts; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Audiences/Spectators; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Royalty; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Children; Boys; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Events/Occasions
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Individual Portraits; Performing Arts; Audiences/Spectators; Costumes; Tents; Events/Occasions
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Events/Occasions; Audiences/Spectators; Tents
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Costumes; Performing Arts; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits; Tents; Events/Occasions; Women; Men; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Furnishings
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Umbrellas/Parasols; Women; Men; Events/Occasions; Tents; Audiences/Spectators
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)